// creating an array and passing the number, questions, options, and answers
let questions = [
  {
    numb: 1,
    question: "What is the correct future tense form of the verb 'to eat'?",
    answer: "will eat",
    options: ["eat", "eating", "will eat", "ate"],
  },
  {
    numb: 2,
    question: "Which word is an auxiliary verb used in the future tense?",
    answer: "will",
    options: ["is", "will", "have", "do"],
  },
  {
    numb: 3,
    question: "Which sentence is in the simple future tense?",
    answer: "We will visit our grandparents next week.",
    options: [
      "She is go to the park.",
      "He plays tennis every weekend.",
      "We will visit our grandparents next week.",
      "I am cooking dinner now.",
    ],
  },
  {
    numb: 4,
    question: "Which sentence is NOT in the future tense?",
    answer: "I am studying for my exam.",
    options: [
      "He will be sleeping soon.",
      "I am studying for my exam.",
      "They are going to the movies tonight.",
      "We will have dinner at 7 PM.",
    ],
  },
  {
    numb: 5,
    question: "What is the correct future tense form of the verb 'to swim'?",
    answer: "will swim",
    options: ["swam", "swimming", "swim", "will swim"],
  },
  {
    numb: 6,
    question: "What time _____ you _____ the party tomorrow?",
    answer: "will / leave",
    options: ["will / leave", "will / leaving", "did / leave", "do / leave"],
  },
  {
    numb: 7,
    question: "We _____ a new car next month",
    answer: "will buy",
    options: ["buy", "buying", "will buy", "bought"],
  },
  {
    numb: 8,
    question:
      "Which sentence uses the negative form of the simple future tense correctly?",
    answer: "They won't travel to Japan next summer.",
    options: [
      "He will not going to the party tonight.",
      "They won't travel to Japan next summer.",
      "We aren't will study for the test.",
      " She isn't will work on the project tomorrow.",
    ],
  },
  {
    numb: 9,
    question:
      "Choose the correct form of the simple future tense for the sentence 'They _______ to the beach next weekend.'",
    answer: "are going",
    options: ["going", "will going", "are going", "went"],
  },
  {
    numb: 10,
    question: "Which sentence is a question sentence in Simple Future Tense?",
    answer: "Will you travel to Bali next month?",
    options: [
      "They will have a picnic next Sunday.",
      "He will not watch a movie tonight.",
      "Will you travel to Bali next month?",
      "She will cook dinner for us tonight.",
    ],
  },
  // you can uncomment the below codes and make duplicate as more as you want to add question
  // but remember you need to give the numb value serialize like 1,2,3,5,6,7,8,9.....

  //   {
  //   numb: 6,
  //   question: "Your Question is Here",
  //   answer: "Correct answer of the question is here",
  //   options: [
  //     "Option 1",
  //     "option 2",
  //     "option 3",
  //     "option 4"
  //   ]
  // },
];
